From now on,
you are no longer in any position of Lin Group.
Come to me when you figure it out.
Behave yourself.
Who am I?
Why am I still alive?
The Bai Qiang case was transferred to police.
According to the clues,
S Club is involved in a group of fraud.
As for the details of the investigation,
according to the regulations,
I can't say much.
S club,
do you know it?
I also studied there.
I've been on this path
for too long.
But
this is not enough to keep an eye on her.
We need more direct evidence
to prove that she killed Wang Jiming
and even Lin Muyun,
not just what she did three years ago.
Evidence.
By the way,
when did you know
the real identity of Wang Jiming?
Mr. Lin Muyun, the chairman of Lin Group,
sent me to the UK.
Wang Jiming
is the biological son of Chairman Lin.
I remember you told me before you went abroad
that he lost his father when he was young.
Besides you,
who else knows his identity?
Uncle Chen,
have all his things been cleaned up?
Yes, Mr. Wen.
Mr. Lin's personal items
have been packed and sent to his apartment.
There will be no Mr. Lin in the company.
All his permissions are frozen.
Understand?
Yes.
Notify the Security Department
to strengthen the control
of all exits in the building,
especially
the underground garage
and the logistics channel.
I don't want to see
any unrelated people.
This is all you've found, right?
Yeah.
Thank you for coming with me.
No need to thank me.
I'm just your friend.
Let's go.
Let's go inside and have a look.
Are you from the Lin Group?
What can I do for you?
Director,
we just want to know
if there was an old man
named Chen Shusheng
here three years ago.
You mean
the driver of Chairman Lin, right?
I remember him.
But
he died of illness
three years ago.
We just want to know
if he has any relatives.
After all,
caring for the families of deceased employees
is a tradition of Lin Group.
Chen Shusheng
has a nephew.
He handled the funeral affairs.
Wait a moment.
I'll find his contact information.
Okay.
Brother,
this is
the final audit draft backup
of the funds transferred through the Nancheng land project.
Wen Shiyi is very likely
to use this to blackmail you,
making you take the blame.
Yaru,
you shouldn't get involved in these things.
Brother,
Don't you understand yet?
Wen Shiyi is a lunatic.
She sacrificed Lin Jiming for the IPO today,
and she can sacrifice us for profit tomorrow.
She's using you.
Brother,
tell me everything
you know about Wen Shiyi.
Otherwise,
you'll be the next
to be discarded by her
after being used up.
Hello,
is Chen Bing here?
Who
are you?
Why are you looking for him?
My uncle
passed away three years ago.
He had stomach cancer.
He didn't live long.
Why do you care about these old stories?
Well,
he has been buried for three years.
Mr. Chen,
we just want to know more about
the situation before Mr. Chen left.
It's very important to us.
It's about...
Mr. Chen,
I heard that
you have been taking care of Mr. Chen
since he retired.
Kind of.
His disease
was found in the late stage.
He died after a few days of suffering.
I didn't
do much to help.
The director of the nursing home told us
that Mr. Chen stayed there
for only a short period of time
and insisted on leaving.
His subsequent treatment seemed to have been interrupted.
May I ask why?
Old people, you know,
are stubborn.
He felt that he was dying
and didn't want to die in the nursing home.
He didn't want to waste money on treatment either.
He insisted on going home.
What can I do?
Mr. Chen,
did Mr. Chen
leave anything behind for you?
Like documents,
keys to a bank safe,
or did he say anything special?
You...
Stop asking.
He's just an old man.
What could he possibly have?
I...
Everything that should be burned has been burned.
That's very strange, Mr. Chen.
We just asked the nursing home.
When Chen Bo left,
although his mental state was not good,
according to the records of the institution,
if he actively cooperated with the treatment,
there was still a possibility of extending his life.
And,
after he left the nursing home,
he didn't go back to your home,
but rented a house in an old community
until he passed away.
This doesn't seem like
a choice someone who doesn't want to waste money would make,
let alone
someone who has burned
everything that should be burned.
Mr. Chen Bing,
I just want to tell you,
concealing the truth
sometimes carries greater risks
than revealing it.
Are you sure you want to take on everything alone?
Mr. Chen,
I'm begging you.
Uncle Chen was a good man.
He wouldn't want those people to get away with it,
while the real culprit
gets away with it.
It's not that my uncle didn't want to be cured.
He just didn't want to live anymore.
He said
he knew too much.
Death would be a clean slate.
He didn't want to drag me into this.
Before he died,
he left something for me.
It's hidden in the iron box on the beam of his house.
He said
it was something that could blow up the world.
He asked me not to take it out for my whole life,
unless
someone comes to investigate the truth.
What is it?
What did Mr. Chen leave?
It's
the will of Mr. Lin.
It's clearly
written on it
the Lin Group
will be inherited by
Wang Jiming.
Su Wei, the fool,
kept telling me
she had it done.
But
she got herself into trouble.
She won't say anything, right?
We shouldn't
We shouldn't tie our fate
to someone else.
Mr. Wen,
what about Mr. Lin?
What about Jiming?
What do you mean?
Are you really not going to
let him return to the Lin Group?
Let's talk about it later.
He needs to calm down now.
Zhanshan,
this is just a temporary measure.
You've seen
Jiming's current state.
He can't return to the company.
I'm just temporarily taking over for him.
No matter what,
he's still my son.
The Lin Group
will be his in the future.
Alright.
Keep an eye on him.
Recently,
don't let him speak out of turn.
Okay?
Yes.
Honey,
it won't be long.
I'll make sure everyone knows the truth.